Djebbes Rabah

+213.558.605.921 • Algeria Constantine • Rabahwork@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/rabahdjebbes

PYTHON/DJANGO DEVELOPER

System Programming | Python Development | Backend Development

Reliable, energetic and resourceful Python/Django Developer with over three years of experience writing and testing code, debugging programs and integrating applications with third-party web services for multiple campaigns in diverse industries.

Expertise in coding, designing, deploying, and debugging development projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Turing.com / 2021 - Current

Remote

Python/Django Developer

- Responsible for developing back-end components.
- Responsible for connecting applications with third-party web-based services.
- Responsible for working with front-end developers to integrate full-stack projects.

Upwork.com – 2019 - Current

Freelance

Python/Django Developer

- Responsible for handling development projects typically on the server-side.
- Responsible for helping organizations with their technological framework.
- Responsible for creating applications as well as designing frameworks for the code.

Fiverr.com / 2019 - Current

Freelance

Python/Django Developer

- Responsible for handling development projects typically on the server-side.
- Responsible for helping organizations with their technological framework.
- Responsible for creating applications as well as designing frameworks for the code.

EDUCATION

University Of Constantine - *Algeria, Constantine* Bachelor's Degree - Robotics, 2020-2024

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Expertise in Backend Technologies and Frameworks.
- Knowledge of Front-end Languages and Frameworks.
- Familiarity with Database Management Systems and Web Hosting Platforms.
- Excellent Communication Skills with a Focus on Team-building and Customer Relations.
- Outstanding Organizational, Multitasking, and Problem-solving Abilities.

AWARDS AND CERTIFICATION

• Developing Applications with SQL, Databases, and Django

IBM

• DevOps and Build Automation with Python

Learn Quest

Crash Course on Python

Google

• Introduction to Data Science in Python

University of Michigan

• Certificate of Language Ability

Emmersion

SPOKEN LANGUAGES

- **Arabic** Native or bilingual proficiency
- **English** Native or bilingual proficiency
- **French** Conversational proficiency